born-bam.myshopify.com 2015-05-05

# Privacy Policy – 3Claps

**BACKGROUND**

When you purchase products on 3CLAPS.COM, we ask you for personal information. We use this information to process your orders and to communicate with you about the status of your orders. We also use your email address to send you invitations to fashion shows, as well as messages about special offers, promotional announcements, and surveys. Occasionally, we send our customers special offers and promotional information via postal mail, using the shipping address provided. If you no longer want to receive the announcements or postal mail, you can email HELP@3CLAPS.COM and request us to stop sending such announcements to you.

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION**

When you place your first order with 3CLAPS.COM, we ask you for your full name, physical address, telephone number and credit card number so we can ship your order. We use your telephone number only if there is an order-related issue, not for marketing purposes. Our server stores this information so that placing future orders will be quicker and easier. If you want to update your address or change credit cards, go to your Account page and make the appropriate changes. You must be signed in to access your account.

We also track your order and billing history. We will use this information to process your orders and communicate with you about your orders. We also use your email address to send you invitations to fashion shows, as well as messages about 3CLAPS special offers, promotional announcements, and surveys. We also use this information to stay abreast of the buying trends of our customers.

**VIEWING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION ON 3CLAPS.COM**

You can always access the personal information you have provided to 3CLAPS by going to your Account page. You can make changes to this information to update your account anytime.

**COOKIES**

Upon visiting 3CLAPS.COM, cookies are placed on your computer’s hard drive. (Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive.) Cookies allow us to track the items you purchase, and help us match your address and credit card information with your order so you don’t need to retype the information each time you visit our site.

If your browser is set to not accept cookies, you will not be able to purchase items on 3CLAPS.COM.

We also use cookies to gather usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to our site and its various pages. We analyze this data to assess our product lines offered on our site. Automatically logged information is also used to analyze trends and to administer the site.

**DISCLOSURE**

Except as described in this section, we will not sell, rent or disclose your personally identifying information to third parties.

In order to ship and track merchandise, we make your name and address available to such companies as FedEx. In no instance is FedEx allowed to use your personal information for any other purpose.

We provide analyses of our users in the aggregate to our vendors and prospective vendors. We do this so that we and our vendors can understand you better, and so we can keep bringing you the latest and most current fashions and fashion accessories. At no time, however, will we disclose personal information about specific users.

Customers shall be notified via email for updates to this policy. 3Claps will obtain email consent from any user if the company is going to be using the information collected in a manner different from that stated when the customer registered.

**SECURITY AND ACCESS**

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

You can access your Account from every page on the site to update and correct your name, email address, password, postal address, credit cards, and mailing list preferences. Please note that you must be signed in to 3CLAPS.COM to access this information.

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**PAYMENT**

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

Loading...
